Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ geethasrinivas (LinkedIn) www.mediamint.com/ (Company)

Top Skills

PeopleSoft SuccessFactors BrassRing

Honors-Awards
Clients Favorite Award - Q1 2016

Geetha Srinivas Pasupulati

Talent Advisor - Talent Acquisition @ Amazon (Reach me on pasupg@amazon.com) : 10000+ Linkedin Connections Hyderabad

Summary

I'm a Recruiting Professional who strives to hire the best minds with right fit for Top Tech world, someone who loves the data & tools by raising the bar while wowing the stakeholders in an extremely competitive market.

For me recruiting is an art & a science too - it is like finding the elusive piece in the jigsaw - in time!

16+ years of experience in Talent Engagement, Talent Management and Business Process Management primarily in the Recruitment/RPO/Staffing/HR industry.

Expertise in Executive Hiring/Networking, Process
Improvement, Vendor Management, Candidate Engagement
Programs, Event Management. Design & implementation of talent
acquisition strategies & solutions in the Technology for both high
value & high volume hiring

Domains Worked on Technology,ecommerce, Manufacturing, Pharma, IT, ITES, BFSI, Engineering, Telecom, Gaming

Experience

Amazon

Talent Acquisition at Amazon Development Centre (India) Pvt. Ltd. November 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Hiring Software Development Engineer II - Excellent at Algo, Data Structures, System Design, HLD and LLD with minimum of 4 years experience. If interested please send me your resume at pasupg@amazon.com

MediaMint

Head - Talent Acquisition March 2015 - November 2016 (1 year 9 months)

Page 1 of 4

MediaMint is an online media company that provides real-time global services to multiple countries in the areas of product strategy consulting, product development and operational support across a variety of functional areas for Web publishers, Demand-side platforms, Ad Agencies, Display, Video and Mobile ad networks.

Electronic Arts
Talent Specialist- Talent Aquisition, EA
April 2011 - March 2015 (4 years)
Hyderabad

Electronic Arts Inc. (EA), headquartered in Redwood City, California, is the world's leading interactive entertainment software company. Founded in 1982, the company develops, publishes, and distributes interactive software worldwide for video game systems, personal computers, cellular handsets and the Internet. Electronic Arts markets its products under four brand names: EA SPORTS(TM), EA(TM), EA SPORTS Freestyle(TM) and POGO(TM). In fiscal 2008, EA posted GAAP net revenue of \$3.67 billion and had 27 titles that sold more than one million copies. EA's homepage and online game site is www.ea.com. More information about EA's products and full text of press releases can be found on the Internet at http://info.ea.com.

Microsoft

Sr.Client Recruitment Specialist May 2010 - March 2011 (11 months)

Microsoft Global Services India, the Global delivery arm of Microsoft Consulting Services.

The MGSI(Microsoft Global Services India) team is one of the fastest growing organizations. Since its establishment in early 2005, it has been a core delivery engine for delivering complex customer solutions across various Microsoft platforms. Microsoft Services Organization focuses on building leading edge products for specific industry verticals.

Was successful in handling CRM and Axapta profiles for MGSI Biz Apps and worked for BI requirements.

Kenexa - IBM Company
Recruitment Specialist
December 2003 - April 2010 (6 years 5 months)

As an Operations Center Recruiter, was responsible for sourcing, screening and working with the Clients directly to responsible to demonstrate the ability

to research various industries and geographic locations using a variety of methods.

Verizon

Project With Kenexa: Role as Recruitment Specialist February 2009 - July 2009 (6 months)

- Executive Search
- Building Sourcing Strategy
- Screening
- Interviewing
- Full Cycle Recruitment for India Market.

Hired people for metropolitan Cities for Verizon Business India.

Corning Incorporated

Project With Kenexa: Role as Sr.Operational Recruiter March 2005 - January 2009 (3 years 11 months)

As a part of Operational Recruiter for the Project: Corning, I am responsible to Contact requisite number of candidates to assure engagement success and involved in direct sourcing of candidates for assigned requisitions.

Responsible for Sourcing, Screening, Interviewing, Scheduling and working with the Client Recruiter to close candidates for external requisitions.

Microsoft

Project with Kenexa: Role as Sourcing Specialist January 2004 - March 2005 (1 year 3 months)

Microsoft is the visionary technology leader that creates innovative software to help individuals and organizations realize their full potential.

- Sourced candidates using Job boards and other database mining tools.
- Tracked and logged candidate workflow in applicant tracking system.
- Prepared daily/weekly/monthly reports of my candidate data for my superiors
- Participated in bimonthly meetings with the internal/contract Microsoft employees
- AD HOC responsibilities as requested by Staffing Consultant.
- Was involved in ISO Audit

Education

Sikkim Manipal University of Health, Medical and Technological Sciences

MBA, Human Resources · (2008 - 2010)

Allahabad Agricultural Institute

M.Sc IT, Information Technology · (2002 - 2004)

Osmania University PGDBM, HRM · (2002 - 2003)

Osmania University
BCA, Computer Science · (1998 - 2001)

St.Judes